// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does CSS stand for?",
    answer: "Cascading Style Sheet",
    options: [
      "Common Style Sheet",
      "Colorful Style Sheet",
      "Computer Style Sheet",
      "Cascading Style Sheet"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What CSS describes?",
    answer: "CSS describes how HTML elements are to be displayed on screen, paper, or in other media.",
    options: [
      "CSS describes how calculation perform on button click.",
      "CSS describes how HTML elements are to be displayed on screen, paper, or in other media.",
      "Both A. and B.",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is a CSS selector?",
    answer: "A CSS selector is the first part of a CSS Rule. It may an HTML element or pattern of elements.",
    options: [
      "A CSS selector is the first part of a CSS Rule. It may an HTML element or pattern of elements.",
      "A CSS selector is the CSS class name.",
      "A CSS selector is the set of properties that are going to be applied on HTML elements.",
      "A CSS selector is name of CSS file."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In a CSS file, there is a CSS rule for paragraphs tags – what does p can be called?",
    answer: "Selector",
    options: [
      "Attribute",
      "Property",
      "Tag",
      "Selector"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Internal styles are written within the _____ element.",
    answer: "&ltstyle&gt…&lt/style&gt",
    options: [
      "&ltcss&gt…&lt/css&gt",
      "&ltstylesheet&gt…&lt/stylesheet&gt",
      " &ltstyle&gt…&lt/style&gt",
      "Both A. and B."
    ]
  },
 // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

     {
     numb: 6,
   question: "Inline styles are written within the _____ attribute.",
  answer: "style",
   options: [
   "style",
     "css",
      "stylesheet",
      "None of the above"
           ]
   },
   
        {
     numb: 7,
   question: "Can comments also span multiple lines?",
  answer: "Yes",
   options: [
   "No",
     "Sometimes yes or no",   
      "Yes",
       "None of the above"      
     ]
   },
   
   
        {
     numb: 8,
   question: "Which property is used to define the text color?",
  answer: "color",
   options: [
   "Font-color",
     "color",
      "text-color",
       "Both A. and B."
     ]
   },
   
        {
     numb: 9,
   question: "Which property is used to define the background color?",
  answer: "background-color",
   options: [
   "bgcolor",
     "back-color",
      "bg-color",
       "background-color"
     ]
   },
   
        {
     numb: 10,
   question: "From the given options which is/are the valid way to represent a color?",
  answer: "All of the above",
   options: [
   "A valid color name like (blue)",
     "HEX code like (#0000ff)",
      "RGB Value like (rgb(0,0,255))",
       "All of the above"
     ]
   },
   
   
];
